[theme music playing]
GENIE, MAKE A WISH
[birds cawing]
Won't you come with me
to the moment you died?
How could I trust you?
[chuckles softly]
I followed his orders
and bowed before the first human.
Iblis has been my brother for the longest
and my enemy for just as long.
Iblis is trying to kill you,
Ms. Ki Ka-young.
The enemy of an enemy…
is surely a friend?
[tense music plays]
Piss off.
-Why?
-Your face just now.
You were being deceptive.
-Whoa!
-Ooh! What? Did you bite your tongue?
Someone just whacked my master.
Really?
Someone who would beat up Ejllael?
I only know of two.
-[yelling]
-[keys clacking]
One of them is occupied, which means…
[screams]
Oh! I have to get to work
early tomorrow, so I'm off.
[Sade] Good morning, Ms. Ki.
Did something happen?
We're with the police.
[gasps] Did Ejllael report you for
assault? He is a stickler for protocol.
I think you're the one
who's ratting me out right now.
-They're on a missing persons case.
-Ah.
Do you recognize this woman?
This village was her last known location.
[sniffing]
I tend to track things by scent.
Oh. [grunts]
We haven't seen her.
Could I take a picture of this?
[officer] Sure.
Please do get in touch
if anything comes to mind.
[clicks]
[suspenseful music plays]
BLACK HAIR DYE
That's strange. I was just here last week.
Why'd they request another visit so soon?
Anyone home? Ms. Shin Suk-ja?
It's your water filter technician.
[sniffing] Oh!
What's that smell?
-[siren chirps]
-[woman 1] Apparently, she died alone.
[woman 2] Who found her?
Her kids must not have checked in on her.
Why do you always handle things
in such a complicated manner?
If I am to keep accompanying
those who die alone,
I must adapt to human protocol.
I made every report myself
until about 40 years ago.
I was really busy back then.
I'd listen to the dying's last complaints
and file the reports,
all in heavy clothes.
Oh.
I can't.
I can't leave my sick girl behind.
I just can't.
Please give me more time
until my granddaughter gets better.
[sobbing] Please.
You don't have to worry about that.
It's not you.
It's her. [gasps]
[cries] No, it can't be!
Then the police started looking for me.
Because death follows me everywhere.
I'm probably still wanted by Interpol.
I see.
Then why were you hit by Ms. Ki Ka-young?
Fail to consider protocol
when convincing her?
Hmm. The fact that you know
means Iblis already knows too.
-[scoffs]
-[Irem] Of course.
I hear the talk of the day,
and Sade hears the night's.
[sighs]
[Sang-hyeok]
Why are you hogging them both?
This is a fight against myself.
Why is an adult doing this
in broad daylight?
Are you a bum?
No, I'm a respectable genie.
And I'm immortal,
so I'm practically an infant.
Oh. So I'm older than you?
Hey, infant. Move over.
No wonder Ka-young doesn't like you.
[indistinct shouting over arcade game]
[announcer over game] K.O.! Game over!
What did you just say?
Sorry for calling you an infant.
Ki Ka-young doesn't like me?
If anyone should dislike anyone, it's me.
Did she tell you that?
Please tell me everything you know,
Mr. Sang-hyeok.
[Sade] Master.
[indistinct chatter over game]
Ejllael personally went
to the lump of clay's house? Why?
I hear he was being all enchanting,
saying, "Won't you come with me
to the moment you died?"
The moment she died?
That won't be good for me.
And?
When he said that, Master's master
told Ejllael to "piss off" and then just
-went for it.
-[groans]
She doesn't give me dinner
if she's in a mood.
[sighs] I should go check.
Distract the man.
The man?
Ki Ka-young!
[gasps]
Wait, this is my carpet.
Gosh, how could she use it to…
[mutters, grunts]
[hesitates] You're wearing Versac…
You're doing this while wearing that?
Ki Ka-young will be mad.
The only way to train my eye for fashion
is to wear stuff like this every day.
Right, I made hamburger steaks.
Leave some for Ka-young.
She'll be home late.
Where did she go? She wasn't at the auto…
Right.
Today's the fourth.
[gentle music plays]
[Ejllael] Aren't you curious
about what happened?
[soft rumbling, whooshing]
[Iblis] You really are doing
your utmost to die, aren't you?
It's not fair.
What exactly was his purpose
in making you and me meet?
[Iblis] Well, based on your actions,
it couldn't have been to make me happy.
I don't know his intentions,
but if you do die, it'll be at my hands.
If you'd like,
we can say that's the reason we met.
[woman] Yoo Jeong-hwa hasn't
attended class for over a month.
[sighing]
[cell phone vibrates]
-[tense music plays]
-[tensed breathing]
Which room is this?
Spare me the bullshit about privacy
and hand me the key,
or I'll call the police.
She's my daughter,
and the boy she's with is a minor.
-[muffled chatter]
-[beeps]
[Jeong-hwa] So fucking annoying.
They're fucking terrible.
Fucking idiots.
Pull your weight, damn it.
[boy] You suck ass too.
[Jeong-hwa] I'm doing perfectly well
right now.
How long do other people
keep theirs before making it?
The third wish, I mean.
The longest was a guy
who held on to it for 72 years.
[chuckles] Wow.
I get it though.
Caught between the despair
that there's only one left
and the euphoria of knowing
that you still have one,
you don't want to break the spell.
[chuckles wearily]
Tell me.
What did he wish for?
Most humans make
their first wish right away,
afraid that their newfound luck
may vanish.
Then they use their second wish,
patching up the first one
they rushed to make,
cursing themselves
for their failure to wish for more.
And then, they live in hell,
clinging to their final wish.
Seeking something greater,
greater, and greater still.
He made his final wish after 72 years.
He wished for me to forget
that he'd already
made two wishes. [laughs]
[suspenseful music plays]
He found the greatest thing of all.
Does that work?
What do you think?
If you'd like to know, try it.
-[chuckles smugly]
-[suspenseful music intensifies]
[music stops]
[exhales excitedly]
[clears throat]
[gasps] Goodness me.
[Ka-young] Always put the purse
back in its dust bag.
Do not wear on rainy days.
Never ever wear
hot pink Crocs with this outfit.
This outfit goes with
both sneakers and heels.
Keep the shoes simple for a smart look.
And carry this purse.
No fruit knives in the purses.
My goodness, this girl.
I see. So this is how you style them.
Let's see.
Today, I choose you.
-[peppy music plays]
-Oh.
Uh…
[chuckles in delight]
Oh.
[chuckles]
[Mi-ju] 4,000 won?
For one of these?
Goodness me,
4,000 won gets you a loaf of bread.
You're wearing designer heels
and a blouse from the latest collection,
yet this is expensive?
[exhales] You sure are strange.
[chuckles] That I am. Very strange.
Come by my place sometime.
I'll fry you sweet pancakes.
As big as your face. [chuckles]
Just eat one.
The owner here is one of my patients,
and they still need a few more implants.
Then we'd best boost their sales.
Especially if they're
Dr. Choi's patients, no?
All right, let's see.
-[squeals] Too sweet.
-[chuckles]
Two would be pushing it.
An old-fashioned palate
and an ultra-smooth home invite.
What on earth is this lady's deal?
My deal?
I'm a woman
whose life was a teeny bit difficult
but has recently become
a teeny bit more fun. Mm?
[both laughing]
[Mi-ju] Mm. Go on. Try it. [chuckles]
Mm!
[Heung-rye] Something's definitely off.
Pan-geum may be having
the time of her life in Hawaii,
but there's no way
she wouldn't be in touch for this long.
Some crazy crap is going down.
I just know it.
Right?
It's one thing not to call us,
but she could at least answer our calls.
And it's odd that the moment she left,
a total stranger moved in.
Just now, I saw that young woman
giggling away over cookies with Dr. Choi.
The other night,
I actually saw that girl and Ka-young
digging up Pan-geum's chili field.
I wonder what that was about.
The chili field? Goodness gracious.
Ka-young finally went and did it.
What if she killed her grandma
and buried her?
-There's no way.
-Come on, Heung-rye.
What do you mean there's no way?
The young bitch must be her accomplice!
What are you waiting for? Call Chang-sik!
Ah.
She's a guest at our house
for a six-month countryside stay.
Cut the crap.
If she's only staying for six months,
why'd she come out of Pan-geum's room?
[Chang-sik] Now, now. Calm down, everyone.
Our village elders have reasonable
suspicions given the circumstances,
so you'd best answer honestly.
So, where has your grandma gone?
Hawaii. She said it was her dream
when she was young.
She couldn't pick Miss Korea or Hawaii
and regretted missing both.
Hawaii?
"You go to Hawaii." That Hawaii?
All by her merry self?
Why are you still going on about old news?
-She went to Hawaii.
-Yes?
But she's not answering her damn phone!
-Oh.
-She went quietly by herself.
See? She just said "she went"!
I told you she killed her!
-[gasps]
-And this outsider's your accomplice?
Goodness, dearie.
How could you say something so horrific?
Dearie?
[tense music plays]
[hesitates]
Don't you all call each other that
out in the countryside?
That's what they do on TV.
[chuckles nervously]
Look at how this minx
is squinting her eyes like this.
Look at her.
Who do you think you're fooling?
You call your grandma right now.
I want to see her with my own eyes!
She's right. Aren't you even worried?
None of us can get hold of her.
What did I tell you? She can't call her.
Just spit it out. You did away
with your grandma, didn't you?
What kind of--
You can't. Mm.
[line connects, rings]
[Chang-sik] Hey.
-[line ringing]
-It's ringing right now.
It'll ring, but she won't answer.
MS. OH PAN-GEUM
CONNECTING
-[line connects]
-Huh?
Yes, hello? What is it?
Has something happened?
I'm here in Hawaii.
Right, so you're doing fine.
It's me, Chang-sik.
-Say hello, everyone.
-[upbeat music plays]
[Chang-sik] Is it night over there?
Gosh, that's so cool.
[Pan-geum] Just look at the ocean
over there. Amazing, isn't it?
-Hand it over!
-[Chang-sik] It's a video call!
It's a vid--
You sure are something.
How could you go all by yourself?
I heard you had a spare ticket and all!
[Chang-sik] Hand it here. Let's all see.
Hey, look at you!
A flower wearing flowers! [laughs]
Goodness, you're all pretty and glowing.
Pan-geum, why didn't you answer our calls?
And when are you coming back?
Uh… I was thinking of staying
for a few more months.
Ka-young is all grown up now,
and my eldest daughter asked me
to come and live with her.
And… Hello?
[distorted] Hello?
[Ok-nam] What's wrong with the connection?
The reception here is…
-Hello?
-Right, on your way back, I'd love…
Some jojoba oil, but the line cut out.
Either way, you all saw that, right?
We all suspected Ms. Ki for nothing!
At ease. Everyone, disperse!
Honestly. Let's go pick some strawberries!
Why didn't you call her
when we first asked?
You kept talking in circles,
like you were hiding something.
Of course I'd suspect you!
You're not exactly normal.
[somber music plays]
[Ka-young sighs]
Uh… [sighs]
I thought I'd drop by the village hall,
but I'll lie low from now on.
I caused you such a headache.
[sighs]
Didn't you say you'd come up with
perfectly flawless wishes? Ha.
You're grateful as hell?
So it's moments like these.
This is what I get…
for being selfish
and making wishes to Satan.
[somber music continues]
[sighs]
Hello.
I'm a student studying
how to decipher facial features. [gasps]
-I see you have such a pure soul.
-[scoffs]
Of course. I would.
I'm a spirit.
But life's giving you trouble?
How did you…
I ought to take pleasure
in my enemy's misfortune, but I don't.
-Why might that be?
-Right. Of course you're unhappy.
I see an ancestor of yours
died on the road.
My ancestor lives on, immortal.
It's my brothers who died far from home.
Almost all of them died
in the war against the angels.
I'm just setting the record straight.
[pats ground]
Uh… [chuckles nervously] Is that so?
Well, best wishes to you.
Where are you going?
That was just the prologue.
The war lasted 300 years!
[music playing faintly over speakers]
Heading home from work?
Ms. Lee?
[gasps] I'm sorry. Could you repeat that?
I'm deaf,
so my responses are delayed.
I need to read your lips.
[woman] Here's your latte.
I had no idea.
Your latte's ready.
I've had a lot of time to practice
because I was born this way.
Because one shouldn't hear
the secrets of heaven.
Excuse me.
What was that?
Sounded like the line, "Lucifer has come
to the school for Satans."
[Irem] I was born
from a single breath of white smoke,
drawn from a hookah pipe and exhaled
by my master, the angel Ejllael.
When my master made me,
he blocked my ears.
-Lest I trill the secrets of heaven.
-Hey, stop! You've been so nice to me!
-Don't get bored with me!
-[screaming]
-[Iblis] Hey, that's the road!
-[honking]
-[tires screech]
-[thuds]
[Iblis] Oh, dear.
[indistinct excited chatter]
[man] All right, you're free to enter now!
[Iblis] Hmm?
Hmm?
-[excited chatter]
-Mm?
[clamoring]
[cheering, clamoring]
I don't think I've seen you here before.
Auntie!
I told you, that's not the bathroom!
Go outside!
So you must all be family.
What do you say?
Do you want in on a round?
But I don't know what that is.
And, most importantly,
I'm broke. [laughs]
Don't you worry about that.
You'll learn the rules as you play,
and I can lend you some money.
Let's start with a million
with 10% deducted as interest.
Wait, you're just handing me
something so precious?
[gasps] Thanks.
You must be the leader of this tribe.
Don't get nervous.
I'll approach you slowly.
[siren wailing]
You've dodged the molestation charges.
So people over there really do
greet each other by touching noses.
[both laugh]
You may leave once your guardian arrives.
My guardian?
Wait, can't I just go?
You saw me get beaten up
last time, didn't you?
Molestation?
First you dine and dash. Now molestation?
-Wear the clip.
-[sighs]
-Wear it!
-[knuckles cracking]
The thing is,
this all came about because…
Seriously, this is so unfair.
[Ka-young grunting] Get over here.
Unfair? This is unfair?
Come here. [grunting]
Get over here.
Two.
I have two left.
SA FAMILY GAMJA-TANG
[excited chatter in distance]
DEPOSIT, KI KA-YOUNG
10,000,000 WON
[breathing heavily]
This is driving me nuts.
CHEONGPUNGHO BANK
The psycho's filthy rich, but her
daily transfer limit is ten million!
That won't do.
If we move it all at once,
they'd investigate immediately.
I'll figure out the rest myself.
Here's my second wish.
Increase Ki Ka-young's transfer limit
to the maximum.
[tense music plays]
[knock on door]
Why would you lock the break room door?
Get out here.
Ki Ka-young is asking for you.
I want to increase my transfer limit
to the maximum.
[chuckles, inhales excitedly]
Sure.
The maximum is 50 million.
Fill out the blanks
here and here. [clears throat]
At the bottom here too.
[suspenseful music plays]
[laughs cunningly]
[printer whirring]
DEPOSIT, KI KA-YOUNG
50,000,000 WON
[gasps, screams]
GU BO-GYEONG, JULY 12, 2024
MADE HER SECOND WISH
INCREASE KI KA-YOUNG'S TRANSFER LIMIT
Every human I've seen loved money the most
and hated losing it the most.
Don't you?
Didn't you see me write fast
because I hate it?
But if it's to validate humanity,
losing money would be worthwhile.
-It would prove my arrogance.
-[scoffs]
So stop gloating. I know I'm losing.
Why were you in the water?
-Hmm?
-Those bubbles were you, right?
I'll go wherever I want.
It's not like you own the ocean. [scoffs]
Is there anything you hate in particular?
Like garlic?
Or a stake?
-Or a cross?
-[laughing]
I particularly hate you.
Get out.
[upbeat pop music playing]
Hey, Mi-ju. You found your way here.
I'm here, yes, but I'm not sure
a rookie like me could do anything.
I was a complete mess
when I first started.
Played any other sports in the past?
I did a little yoga in the past.
I could get my foot up to my neck
and was pretty flexible.
But I can't go there anymore.
I've been thinking,
I may as well learn something
I could use to protect someone.
-Oh. Hit this. Show me what you've got.
-[both] Whoa.
-Holy smokes!
-Hey, what was that?
-[gasps]
-You'll get us in big trouble!
Mi-ju, are you loaded?
I think you might have to replace this.
Really? Did they attach it with glue?
I'm joking, of course.
-[Mi-ju] Joking?
-[laughs]
[Mi-ju] Bring it on. Get over here.
[Min-ji] Whoa!
About that mansion.
Do you think everyone
in the front yard was family?
Didn't they look
more like guards than family?
No. You can't fool these eyes.
They're not family or guards.
Something is happening
in this peaceful village of mine.
They were…
an army.
-An army?
Yes. Military.
GOBLIN STATIONERY
[light thudding]
Mister, where did you get that money?
-You've always been broke.
-[Ka-young] Stop right there!
Why?
Empty your pockets.
[chuckling]
Certain dark channels were involved.
All right. It's on me today.
-Really? You're being serious, right?
-[laughs]
-What's with your arms?
-Certain dark family matters are involved.
By the way, do you want to know a secret?
You have to keep this secret.
[mother] Sang-hyeok, run. Quickly!
[man] Get back here, you little shit!
[mother] Why take it out on him
when you're short on cash?
[man] That's why I said
get an overdraft account, you bitch!
[mother] I can't with my credit score,
you fucking asshole!
[Sang-hyeok] I saw an angel.
You did?
I see them occasionally too.
Okay, I'm starting.
I'm being serious.
So I prayed.
I asked them to make
my mom's boyfriend disappear.
That jerk you saw doesn't grant wishes.
You have no idea how selfish he is.
Don't believe me, then.
Seriously, though,
as soon as I'm a bit bigger,
I'd probably be able to beat him up.
But it just takes too long to grow up.
Okay, give me 100 won.
But you have a lot of money now.
I'm saying I'll grant that wish for you.
But nothing in this world is free.
You wouldn't know, but the true wish
specialist is… Woo-hoo! I won! [laughing]
I'll trust you this once.
I deliberately lost
a 100-won match to you.
What? Wow. [laughs]
You're worse than Satan.
All right.
It's just until you become an adult.
You're 12 years old right now,
so I'll have them maul him just enough
to keep him bedridden for 7.5 years.
[screaming]
[groaning]
My arms. My legs.
-[Iblis] I know this face.
-[whimpers]
Who are you?
-Send help! A man's dying out here!
-[laughs]
A man?
I don't see a man here.
You beat a 12-year-old
and call yourself a man?
Even Satan would shed tears…
Good job holding back.
In BC,
I fought for three centuries
to protect my brothers.
Today, in 2024 AD,
I start yet another war
for the sake of a brother.
Sang-hyeok is an enemy,
but he's also a comrade.
And he chose to become my friend.
That is the reason
for your current suffering. [whistles]
[yelping]
Help me!
-Help me! I was wrong. Please!
-[snarling]
How unlucky.
[screaming] Help me!
My specialty is killing, not saving.
-[dogs growling]
-[man screaming]
[somber music plays]
Why do you keep following me?
Got nothing better to do?
I had to get him
from the desert back to Korea,
call an ambulance,
and frame him as delusional!
Why stir up chaos in the modern world?
Why are you suddenly pretending
to be a good guy?
You know, I've been thinking about that.
Ever think I was originally the good guy,
and you were the bad one?
I shall use a very blunt scythe
when I slit your throat.
So one strike won't do.
See?
You and I are no different.
Do you even have time for this?
Don't you need to go see Ki Ka-young?
I guess you're not up
for another beating. [chuckles]
What?
Concerned I'll go see her again?
What did you even mean to show her?
What, my cruelty?
Or the wishes she made?
That's why I was punished
for 983 years, no less.
Isn't that enough?
[laughs]
How laughable.
We have lived an eternity,
so that period of less than 1,000 years
was hardly punishment.
I've inspected every element,
and there are no issues with the watch.
Really?
I'm sure the watch hands spun backwards.
Incredibly fast at that.
I've been working here for over ten years,
and I've never had an inquiry like this.
Moreover, it's just impossible, ma'am.
[ticking]
[rapid ticking]
So I really can't let myself in?
What the hell does it say?
It says you shouldn't shake it.
That an ill-tempered genie
might get angry.
[clicks]
TRANSLATE
SHELF LIFE IS INFINITE
FROM DATE OF REMAKING: OCTOBER 24, 1061
So he lied.
If it was the year 1061,
and he said he was confined for 983 years,
he's 20 years short.
It couldn't have been a housing scam.
What is this?
[sniffing]
[in Mongolian] Who are they?
What have they been doing there all day?
Should we bring it up?
[in Korean] Why the intense stares?
What are they looking at all day?
I'm Chauffeur Kim, a former member
of the Reconnaissance Unit.
I sense some intense eyes on us.
Two in the bushes.
Two more in the mansion.
Perhaps more.
Boss…
[sighs]
…what kind of life have you led?
I have no other choice.
You can trust me, sir.
Apologies, sir,
but may I ask what you are waiting for?
I'm waiting
for my dad.
This is where I lost my way.
I remember the smell of my dad's car.
[sniffing]
My younger brother, Ha-neul. Kim Ha-neul.
He'll be looking for me.
Dad?
Is this short-term memory loss
or something?
What on earth
have you gotten tangled up in, sir?
-[woman 1] That's insane.
-[woman 2] She sure is something.
[woman 3] Can you believe he told me
I can't leave work until she gets here?
I swear the guy's nuts.
-[woman 1] This is crazy.
-She's here.
-Is something wrong?
-[scoffs]
I honestly can't believe this.
Come with me.
What the hell is going on here?
Why is the money
in Ms. Ki Ka-young's account
being transferred into your account
every day, Ms. Gu?
Are you embezzling?
How could you say such a thing?
It's the first I'm hearing of it too.
[laughs incredulously]
For the past two weeks,
there have been transfers of ten million,
then 50 million won every day,
and this is news to you?
This is so damn unfair!
Are you saying I should spend
all my time checking my account?
Huge amounts
were being transferred every day,
and you seriously didn't know?
Our logs show you repeatedly accessed
Ms. Ki Ka-young's information.
How do you explain that?
You asked me to sell her our pension plan.
That's why I looked.
To figure out how to convince her!
You saw the logs, so you'll know.
She came in
to increase her transfer limit.
So why are you doing this to me?
Shouldn't you be speaking
to Ki Ka-young about this, not me?
Why, you…
Given the situation, sir,
the Financial Supervisory Service
must already be investigating--
Shut your mouth!
Of course I know that!
Unbelievable.
Ms. Gu, go meet Ms. Ki Ka-young
before the FSS does,
and find out what has happened here.
You're friends, aren't you? Friends!
All of our jobs are on the line now.
Yes, sir.
[ominous music plays]
[in Arabic] I'm back.
Eat up.
[in Korean] Thanks for the book.
HISTORY OF GORYEO
Have you
finally made a decision?
[Iblis] The angels came down
and began slaughtering all genies,
and Ejllael is the one who led the charge.
[chuckles smugly]
[Iblis] The war lasted 300 years,
and I lost most of my brothers
as a result.
Lead the way
to the moment I died.
[Sade growling]
[hoots]
[Ejllael in Arabic] He is displeased
as disasters and droughts
have struck Ifriqiya,
costing countless human lives.
You'd best not provoke them.
Don't overdo it.
Anyway, what is that face you wear?
[in Korean] I chose a face
set to be in high demand
across the world for the next millennium.
I'm speaking in their language now too.
My next wish-maker
is on their way from there. [sniffs]
[suspenseful music plays]
[snarling]
[man in Arabic] Dogs! Wild hounds!
-Run!
-[barking]
[man 2] A pack of wild hounds!
[barking, growling]
Dogs! It's a pack of wild hounds!
[in Middle Chinese]
Just throw that limping boy aside!
[indistinct shouting]
[in Korean] No, don't!
You can't!
-[crying] Don't!
-[boy crying]
-[child Ka-young] Hunbish!
-[growling]
[panting]
[crying]
-[barking]
-[whimpers, screams]
[screaming]
[in Arabic] The time has come
for some wishes.
-[child Ka-young cries, screams]
-[Hunbish screams]
-[screaming]
-[growling]
-[grunts]
-[yelps]
[screaming]
[chiming]
-[tense music plays]
-[whooshing]
[man] It's Iblis! It's Shaytan!
It's Shaytan! Run!
[in Middle Chinese] Where are you going?
Cast the Goryeo bitch aside too!
[in Arabic] Run away!
-[man 2] Save me!
-[men clamoring]
-[gasps]
-[man 3] Hurry, run!
[in Korean] I am Genie, the lamp spirit.
I shall grant you three wishes.
Make them.
Did you say wishes?
No bringing back the dead.
No traveling to the future.
Anything besides that,
your wish…
is my command.
Are you also
from Goryeo, sir?
If you'd like it that way,
let's say it's so.
Now,
make your first wish.
-[Hunbish screaming]
-[dogs growling]
Please save Hunbish.
Please let him live a long, long life.
Please! He can't just die like this.
That's right.
Come with me
to corruption.
-[screaming]
-[gusting]
[man] Run!
[Ibis] Do not blame me.
My young master wishes
for someone to live a long life.
-[thuds]
-[whizzing]
[Iblis] And for a long, lengthy life,
a blood sacrifice must be made.
Desert,
be tainted by this blood.
[dramatic orchestral music plays]
[Iblis] The boy lives,
though the wild hounds will starve.
Now, shall we hear
what your second wish is?
Please make it so that
other children from Goryeo
aren't sold to be animal feed, as I was.
Then I shall cut off the path.
I shall be back soon.
[tense music plays]
[birds cawing]
This is probably around 1041 AD.
Are you sure it was the year 1041?
I'm sure.
I remember it as the time when Iblis
was at his height, deceiving humans.
There was an unusually large number
of deaths that year.
Including yours.
[birds cawing]
You see them, don't you? All those deaths.
All the work of Iblis.
[whimpers]
[panting]
-[growling]
-[gasps]
-[barking]
-[gasping]
[Sade growling]
There they are.
Do you see me there with a scythe?
I haven't seen my original face
in a long time.
I'll change it to this face
so it's less jarring. [snaps fingers]
So your second wish
has also been fulfilled.
The path to Goryeo has been blocked.
Blocking that path
triggered quakes and tsunamis.
With your first wish,
15 of 17 merchants lost their lives,
and due to your second wish,
hundreds of humans died.
That can't be.
I didn't make such wishes.
[in Mongolian, panting] Please help!
[grunts]
[in Korean] Hmm. I guess that makes it 16.
Now, only your final wish remains.
Girl from a foreign land, make your wish.
This is not what I wanted.
What do I do now?
I made the wrong kinds of wishes. [crying]
How foolish.
There's no such thing as the right wish.
To gain something,
something else must be lost.
For someone to live, another must die.
-Sade!
-[growls]
[tense music plays]
-[barking]
-[screams]
-[child Ka-young screams]
-[whistles]
You may say such things, but your
final wish will be "please save me."
-So make your wish.
-[breathing heavily]
[child Ka-young] No.
I accept
whatever punishment.
So please,
make sure…
we are punished.
You and I both.
[tense music plays]
What?
[child Ka-young] It's only fair.
This
is my final wish.
[music intensifies]
[heavy exhale]
You lowly thing. You dare…
You petty human,
molded from mere clay. You dare?
-[breathing heavily]
-[Ejllael laughs]
Behold.
His creations
are truly righteous and beautiful.
You have lost, Iblis.
You remember his words, don't you?
If you happen to meet
even one pure human, you will forever…
-Just wait.
-No, forever!
Wait, just wait!
Righteous? [scoffs]
I'm not sure.
[scoffs] Because really,
there's room for interpretation here.
So would you put in
a good word for me, Brother?
-[scoffs]
-[breathing heavily]
Cut the crap. [laughs]
Is this really the end?
Really?
Hey, come back.
Ejllael.
Get back down here!
[somber music plays]
You lowly clay. You dare…
You lowly being, molded on a Friday.
Mere human who lives
for less than 100 years. You dare!
[melancholy music plays]
[sighs] Do you see?
Your death was so tragic.
Iblis is an evil bastard
who twisted every wish you made,
no matter what it was,
to lead you to corruption.
[gentle music plays]
It wasn't…
rage.
When I saw him in the lamp,
it definitely looked like rage.
But this…
This face…
is undeniably
true sorrow.
[dramatic music plays]
[chokes, groans]
[groans, pants]
How laughable.
[panting]
[screams]
We have lived an eternity,
so that period of less than 1,000 years
was hardly punishment.
[dramatic orchestral music playing]
[groaning, panting]
[groaning]
[music ends]
[gentle ballad playing]